ROBIN TEN BERGE

Vuursteenhof 13 1349 EJ Almere

M: +31 6 43 90 68 38 E: robin@rtbprojects.com

https://www.linkedin.com/ in/robintenberge

https://github.com/rbergenl

Technical Skills

NodeJS

HTML5 / CSS3 / ES6

Angular / React

AWS / Azure

CI/CD

Soft Skills

Communicative

Proactive

Problem solving

Team player

Structured

Certificates

Mobile Web Specialist 2019

AWS DevOps Pro 2019

Java SE8 2017

Scrum Developer 2016

Profile

Robin is a senior full stack web developer with 10+ years experience developing cloud-, pipeline-, frontend- and backend solutions. He is focussed on being productive to deliver high quality products while using best practices. He enjoys helping team members and has a desire to share his gained insights.

Robin has excellent communication skills and knows how to find his way within an organisation. He is a pioneer and takes initiatives to help move an organisation forward with innovation. He embraces new technology, puts them into practice and keeps educating himself.

Scrum Master - "You know how to challenge the team. You have a clear opinion on quality and productivity. And in this way you help bring the team to a higher level."

Product Owner - "Robin is able to take responsibility for a solution. He likes to take the lead in creating a collaborative solution and then also delivers it."

Experience

Senior Web Developer, RTB Projects; Almere — 2009 - Present Freelancing with the goal to deliver web development and IT consultancy to small and large companies.

- Received expert score of the React assessment on Pluralsight by being in the top 2%. Published a React Native application to Google Play Store. And created own website rtbprojects.com with the Gatsby framework utilising React and GraphQL.
- Created a Proof of Concept for growing indoor plants. Built a web app with React/Redux using OAuth. And a mobile app with React Native to make a bluetooth connection to a Raspberry Pi. The device then uses custom NodeJs scripts to connect to the AWS IoT service.
- Created a bot running on AWS for trading cryptocurrency using an exchange platform API. To keep the architecture serverless, it uses a CI/CD pipeline and then stores its trade history in DynamoDB.
- Created a full e-commerce solution with PHP to sell products via internet. This includes frontend and a backend for inventory, order and payment processing (WooCommerce did not exist yet).
- Provided IT consultancy to small companies. This includes support with webhosting and delivery of new Wordpress websites, SEO and analytics implementation.

Senior Full Stack Developer, NS, Utrecht — 2019 - Present Worked as full stack developer in a team responsible for travel information on the website. Taking a leading role in the migration of API's and frontend applications from on-premise into AWS Cloud while improving CI/CD pipelines. The team received a DevOps status, being an example to the organisation.

Senior Consultant, Capgemini, Amsterdam — 2014 - Present Worked as web developer and IT consultant at ABN AMRO in Amsterdam. All assignments were in a complex Agile/Scrum environment with Offshore.

For the Commercial Banking department:

- Lead in setting up the frontend architecture utilising the NodeJS ecosystem. Used Bootstrap 4
 with custom CSS/Sass for styling. Built functionality with Web Components, Angular 2+ and
 vanilla ES6/Typescript. Collaborated with other teams to share the architecture.
- Initiated an organisational change to upgrade the Java web application by pitching a Proof of Concept to management. This upgrade was needed to be able to work with DevOps teams.
- Had a business trip to Hyderabad in India to provide knowledge transfer to the Offshore team.

For the Retail department:

- Delivered the first widget for mobile friendly Internet Banking.
- Collaborated with architects on setting up the frontend for widgets. Used AngularJS 1.6 and Bootstrap 3 as a foundation.
- Setup the framework for unit testing with Jasmine, e2e testing with Protractor and a RESTful stub-server with ExpressJs. Shared it with other teams so they can perform better testing and comply with quality guidelines.
- Setup the foundation for a technical style guide with reusable UI components. Supported other teams in using the frontend architecture and reusable components so they can build and deliver faster.

Project Leader, Wageningen University & Research; Wageningen — 2012 - 2013

Responsible for two IT projects. One Prince2 project to deliver an IT Selfservice Portal. And a
Scrum project to deliver a workflow application for an internal customer. The activities included
making project plans, supporting the teams and communicating with stakeholders.

Education

Windesheim University of Applied Sciences, Zwolle – Business Information Technology, Bachelor degree - 2005 - 2008

- Graduated with honour and one year shortened.
- Had two internships. One in New Zealand at Jack & Di's Lakeview Accommodation to optimise
 the reservation process and systems (grade: A+). And a final internship at Ernst & Young to
 develop a method to conduct strategic business information planning (grade: A+).

Additional

Interested in other cultures and meeting new people by doing volunteering projects or adventurous travel. For example backpacking in New Zealand (2007) and a hitchhike trip to Asia (2008). Also did a youth leader training in Russia (2012) and performed as group leader for an international volunteering project in The Netherlands (2012).

Played basketbal for a while (2000-2014), but then did triathlon (2014-2020) and this year started with basketbal again.

Became a husband (2020) and a father in (2021).

Skill Matrix	Knowledge (level)		dge	Experience (years)
Frontend				
HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript			Х	10+
NodeJs ecosystem (incl. NPM and Webpack)			Х	6
ECMAScript 6, Typescript and PWA's			Х	5
React and Angular (incl. Redux and NgRx)			Х	4
Testing frameworks: the latest being Jest and Cypress			Х	5
Backend				
ExpressJs (incl. OAuth and GraphQL)			Х	5
RESTful API integrations (JSON or XML) incl. Swagger			Х	5
Linux		Х		4
MySQL and MongoDB		Х		3
PHP and Java (Kotlin)		Х		3
Platforms				
Wordpress			Х	6
Microsoft Azure			Х	2
Amazon Web Services			Х	4
Google Cloud Platform (incl. Firebase)		Х		3
Google Digital Marketing (incl. Tag Manager, SEO and Analytics)		Х		5
Practices				
Agile/Scrum			Х	7
CI/CD (Git, Jenkins, Webpack, SonarQube, Nexus and Docker)			X	4
DevOps		Х		3